

Minhajuddin Kasman AR, S.T., PNIIT

Web Developer

Proactive, IT and Data enthusiast who is well organized and skilled at balancing the needs of clients in both personal and professional capacities. Strong work ethic and positive attitude. Highly effective in fast-paced work environments. Accurate, assertive, and adaptable. Experienced in projects with various range of clients including individual, organizations, companies, start-ups, etc.

Jl. Bacang, Gang G, No.17 Rawasar, Cempaka Putih Jakarta Pusat, DKI Jakarta

+62 822 2673 2225 didinkha@gmail.com https://mnhjddn.github.io

SKILLS

PHP, Codelgniter, JavaScript, JQuery, CSS, Bootstrap, ES6, React.js, Laravel, OOP, IS/IT Strategic Planning, Requirement Analysis, UML Diagrams, Git, Ms. Office

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2018

Computer Science Academy of Ternate

IT Staff

- > Remotely maintained PC in IT laboratories
- > Developed the academy's official website

July 2019 - July 2020

Indonesia Mengajar Foundation

Full-Stack Web Developer

- > Developed Indonesia Mengajar official website
- > Developed Advanced Recruitment System for Associate Teachers
- > Worked as IT Administrator (Managed IT Assets, Emails, Infrastructures)

EDUCATION

2013 - 2017

Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering (S.T.)

- > Assistant Lecturer of Windows App Development Course
- > Graduated with honors: Cum Laude

2013 - 2017

National Institute of Information Technology

Professional Diploma in Information Technologies (PNIIT)

> Graduated with honors: 3.93 GPA

2019 - Now

University of Indonesia

Master of Information Technology (MTI)

- > Current GPA: 3.34 out of 4.00
- > On-going study

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.